<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Zachary Baker</title>
    <link>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Zachary Baker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 18:52:32 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Universe&#39;s Athenaeum</title>
      <link>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/posts/athenaeum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 18:52:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/posts/athenaeum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; Universe&#39;s Athenaeum The Universe&#39;s Athenaeum The Universe&#39;s Athenaeum contains everything that has been written, will be written, and could be written. Well, at least things with a length of less than 856. The possible characters are the lowercase alphabet, the comma, the period, and the space. So how many books are there in this athenaeum? Well with 29 possible characters and ~855 characters in one book, there are 29^855 books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encompas</title>
      <link>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/posts/encompas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 18:34:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/posts/encompas/</guid>
      <description>Encompas Go to encompas.tech to view our site which is hosted via GitHub Pages
Inspiration In a world where a persons values define how they live, being able to accurately determine your stance on world issues is vital. We immediately noticed that all the current quizzes that help determine your stance are extremely outdated, vague, or inaccurate.
What it does Encompas allows users to vizualize where they stand on the political compass via a 4d graph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Location on Number of Lyme Disease Cases</title>
      <link>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/posts/lyme-disease/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 21:25:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/posts/lyme-disease/</guid>
      <description>The Effect of Location on Number of Lyme Disease Cases By Zachary R. Baker and Srishanth Tangedipalli Thomas Jefferson High School for Science and Technology Dr. Kathleen Morrow, Ms. Erinn Harris, and Ms. Julia Litchford
Introduction Lyme Disease has had over 25,000 cases every year in the US since 2007 (Monaghan et al, 2015). It is a vector-borne disease, which means that it is transmitted to humans and other animals by blood-feeding animals, such as ticks or mosquitos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/post/</guid>
      <description>Posts 2022-04-17 | Encompas
2020-12-18 | The Effect of Location on Number of Lyme Disease Cases</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/about/</guid>
      <description>About I am a sophomore at Thomas Jefferson High School for Science and Technology in Northern Virginia. Some things I like to do include crew, coding, playing chess, and more. This site is my portion of the internet. It contains projects, my resume, the occasional blog post, and more. This site was largely inspirited by Jonathan Buchholz1.
This site was made using Markdown as the main language and Hugo as a framework for building the site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Email: zac.r.baker06@gmail.com 2024zbaker@tjhsst.edu Phone Number: 1-703-405-1525 Github: zacbakerr LinkedIn: Zac Baker Public Key: GPG zacbaker.eth </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zacbakerr.github.io/dotMe/resume/</guid>
      <description>I am a rising junior at Thomas Jefferson High School for Science and Technology Extracurriculars Freshman Year Activity Role Froshcomm1 Officer Class Council Officer TJ Crew Coxswain (Men&amp;rsquo;s First Novice Boat) TJ Media Photographer, Cinematographer TJ Speech Member Anthos Capital Intern Freshman Summer Activity Role Speech Camp Counselor Inspirit AI Ambassador Sophomore Year Activity Role Class Council Historian TJ Speech Officer Sysadmin Understudy Inspirit AI Ambassador TJ Crew Coxswain (Men&amp;rsquo;s First Varsity Boat) TJ Media Photographer, Cinematographer Sophomore Summer Activity Role Blockchain Research @ Georgetown Intern Resilient Crew 8-week Resliant Rowing Camp Junior Year2 Activity Role Class Council Historian TJ Crew xxx TJ Speech Officer TJ Media Photographer, Cinematographer Angler&amp;rsquo;s Alliance Treasurer Other Extracurriculars Chess Club Long time casual player.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
